some days ago I received these two text
messages they are from okx a
cryptocurrency exchange and they are
telling me that my account was about to
be canceled and I needed to log in to
verify myself or I would not be able to
withdraw my money I got really worried
for a second but then I remembered I
don't have any money in okex because I
don't even have an account this message
is of course fake it's fishing which as
you know is a technique that scammers
use to steal our passwords they send you
a text that looks legit with a message
that makes you worried and with a link
to the page where you can log into your
account if you get scared go to the link
and login as many people do you will be
doing so on a fake website that looks
like an exact copy of the legit one both
controlled by the attacker who now has
your username and password the URL of
the website will also be not quite right
it might be something like Facebook
login.cc people fall for this kind of
attack very often and that is why it's
so common So to avoid falling for it if
you get a text message via website you
use telling you to log in immediately
and you don't know if it's real or not
but still want to check go to your
laptop open your browser and type the
address of the website manually whatever
you do don't click on the link which is
the opposite of what I did I clicked on
the link which took me to the scam
website that I then proceeded to analyze
and that is what this video is about
today I would like to show you what I
found out about the escam website and
who might be behind it as well as how we
can take down scam websites to protect
people that might click on the link and
fall on the track after clicking on the
link I was taken to the scam website
which really is a copy of the legit okx
website with a cookie banner and
everything it's also translated in
multiple languages the only difference
is that the moment I go to the website a
pop-up shows up telling me to log in
quickly to secure my account when I do
that it takes me to a page where I'm
supposed to log in after I write down my
username and password and hit enter I
get a captcha to solve they really want
to look legit they are even pretending
to care to check if I am a bot or not
before we solve the captcha let's open
our browsers developer tools and go to
the network panel there we will filter
any requests with the word login after
we solve the captcha sure enough our
username and password were sent to a
server that is not okx.com they even
showed me a message saying my password
is wrong so I guess after I submit the
form on their server they go and check
with the real website to see if the
information works or it might be that
whatever I write does not matter and it
will always say a the password is wrong
because I was curious about the scam
server I tried to send wrong or
incomplete requests to it to see what
information they were exposing at first
I realized I could cause a 500 internal
server error but then the server started
speaking Chinese which was interesting
to see where the server was actually
located I went back to the network panel
and there on the login request we can
clearly see a remote address which is
the IP address the server is located at
after a quick Google search it turned
out that the IP of the scam server was
located in North Korea since I don't
know the email address to report has
come website in bukhan AKA North Korea i
instead run a who is search on the
people that registered the domain it
turns out they use a legit company for
this but they paid to have their records
private the good news is that this
search told us that they used a
Singapore company to buy by the domain
and we also found out that they are
using cloudzer name servers as well
domain companies in Claus there both
have pages to report abuse instead of
wasting time and trying to take this
website down by hacking it we can do
something more effective and that is
killing their domain name which means
that those thousands of messages they
send to the victims will be useless
because if someone clicks on the scam
link they will now see a not found error
feeling these abuse forms does not take
a long time and usually legit companies
act very quickly when an abuse report is
submitted it shouldn't take more than a
couple of days for the domain to be dead
reporting scam websites requires no
technical skills so next time that you
get a scam text message if you have some
time you want to help out click on the
link make sure it's a scam website by
looking at the URL go to who that is
make a search find the companies and
Report The Domain to their abuse page
these will be really annoying knowing
for the scammers usually after an abuse
report the whole account gets suspended
which means that if they are hosting
many websites on the same account or if
they use the same company for all their
domains they will all be taken down
thank you for watching this video please
leave a like And subscribe and let me
know in the comments what is the worst
weirdest or funniest scam message you
ever got and don't forget that if you
want to learn to code and you want to do
it for free with me all you have to do
is click the link below and I will see
you there thank you for watching take
care of one another see you on the next
one bye
foreign